<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ed Leonardy</title>
    <link>https://edleonardy.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ed Leonardy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 10:51:41 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://edleonardy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Malino Highlands day Trip</title>
      <link>https://edleonardy.com/travel/2020/malino/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 10:51:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edleonardy.com/travel/2020/malino/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tocha</title>
      <link>https://edleonardy.com/design/2020/tocha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edleonardy.com/design/2020/tocha/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artee</title>
      <link>https://edleonardy.com/design/2020/artee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edleonardy.com/design/2020/artee/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adelaide &amp; Kangaroo Island in 4 Days</title>
      <link>https://edleonardy.com/travel/2019/kangaroo-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 10:51:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edleonardy.com/travel/2019/kangaroo-island/</guid>
      <description>Day 1: Hahndorf, Grange Beach, Fleurieu Peninsula We started our trip with some brunch and coffee in Adelaide, which is the second best way to start an Australian day (obviously second to yum cha, duh). Then we drove to the Hahndorf area, stopping by at Beerenberg to grab the iconic strawberry jam. (warning: do not buy honey products on the mainland if you&amp;rsquo;re planning to go to Kangaroo Island—bringing honey to the island is prohibited by strict quarantine laws to preserve the existing Kangaroo Island honey)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dian Harapan Yearbook</title>
      <link>https://edleonardy.com/work/sdh-yearbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edleonardy.com/work/sdh-yearbook/</guid>
      <description>Private school high school yearbooks in Indonesia often differ quite a bit from the conventional yearbooks. Each student is to have a whole page spread of their name and photo&amp;ndash;and I got to shoot some for a couple students.
      These students&amp;rsquo; class also wanted to have one extra page for a class photo. We went with a rooftop shot with all 26 students.
  Final design     Guys     Girls         </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TICDA</title>
      <link>https://edleonardy.com/work/ticda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edleonardy.com/work/ticda/</guid>
      <description>My very first sponsored project! The first part of the shoot is heavily inspired from product photography pages I see on Instagram with incredible setups so I attempted a DIY shoot with fake grass from my dad&amp;rsquo;s koi pond and his fishing line to suspend the armband! A few sprinkles of water later I got the shot and I guess that day &amp;lsquo;I could do anything&amp;rsquo; (TICDA hehe)
      The second part of the shoot was an outdoor shoot since the brand also focuses on fitness and health motivation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://edleonardy.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edleonardy.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey! I&amp;rsquo;m Ed, born and raised in a small town in the island shaped like the letter k in the middle of Indonesia called Makassar. I lived in Sydney, Australia for 3 years to study and I graduated with a degree in Data Science. I&amp;rsquo;m currently based in Indonesia where I take photographs and create digital designs while planning my travels!
You can contact me on:
 +62 81 222 000 588 info@edleonardy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>